

# Jason Mitchell iOS Developer

devJM.com devjmitchell@gmail.com github.com/devjmitchell

# **ABOUT**

I'm a U.S. Marine veteran that became a self-taught developer, starting in 2013. I'm always eager to learn new things and have had the chance to explore many technologies and work in several different environments. I've attended multiple code camps, security conventions, and developer Meetup events. I'm excited for the future and what it holds for me. I've been a "professional" iOS Developer since 2018.

I read books and watch videos related to Swift and iOS development for fun... and yes, I have an app in the App Store.

# **HISTORY**

#### 5/2018 - Present

iOS Developer @ U-Haul International

Performed as one of two main iOS developers working on the enterprise application for all U-Haul employees. Supported several "legacy" mobile applications used by all Area Field Managers within the organization through bug fixes and updates.

## 1/2018 - 5/2018

iOS Developer @ Freelancer

Consulted with small business leaders, contributing input and guidance in the development of iOS applications.

## 10/2016 - 5/2018

Network Administrator @ Rockford Corporation Worked in a small IT Department, which allowed me to "wear many hats". Devised solutions to automate and streamline the workflow within the department.

# **EDUCATION**

# 2019

Certificate of Distinction 100 Days of Swift by Hacking with Swift

#### 2018

The Complete iOS App Development Bootcamp London App Brewery

## 2016

B.S. Information Systems Security University of Phoenix

## 2014

Certified ScrumMaster Scrum Alliance

## **SKILLS**

## Languages

I've used the following languages: Swift, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

## **Agile**

I enjoy working in agile environments, such as: Scrum. Kanban

## Tools

I'm quick to learn new tools and systems. Some applicable examples are:

Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, JIRA, Sketch

# **INTERESTS**

Running Family Video Editing
Learning Technology Augmented Reality
Coffee Chess Machine Learning

Scrum Master Apollo Group Project Manager Dimension Data Network Admin Rockford Corp iOS Developer Freelancer iOS Developer U-Haul